Guide to the Howard Zinn Papers TAM.542
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series X: Audio-Visual Material, 1957-2009; 448922
  - Subseries X:F: Video Other Formats, 1975, undated; 449286
    - U-Matic Video Cassette: "High School Kids on the Draft", undated; cuid17585; 450108 (Box 84, Cassette 466)
- Series XI: Archived Website, Jul 1, 2010-ongoing; cuid17586; 547000; 1 websites 1 website
  This is the website of Howard Zinn (1922-2010), the noted radical U.S. historian and author of "A People's History of the United States." In addition to a biography and bibliography, the site contains print interviews, essays and commentary, audio and video, and information about The People Speak, the documentary based on the live performances of Howard Zinn and Anthony Arnove's Voices of a People's History of the United States.
  Accruals
  This website is crawled semi-annually.
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript,streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.